cgcareers.org 2016-11-25

# Privacy Policy › About Us › Commongood Careers

###  Introduction

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes the practices of Commongood Careers, Inc. (“Commongood Careers”) with respect to the gathering and use of personal information submitted to Commongood Careers through the Commongood Careers website and job board (the “Website”).

###  Information we collect

Commongood Careers collects certain personal information which is submitted by you when you apply through the Website for a job that is managed by Commongood Careers,  when you submit an application to the General Talent Pool, when you send an email to Commongood Careers, and when you sign up to receive updates and newsletters from Commongood Careers. This personal information may include, but may not be limited to:

  * Name
  * Employer name
  * Home or office mailing address
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone, cellular and fax numbers

In addition, when you visit the Website, we may collect technical and navigational information, such as computer browser type, Internet protocol address, pages visited, and average time spent on our Website. This information is gathered through the use of cookies. A cookie is a small data text file that a website server writes to your hard-drive when you visit the website. A cookie assigns a unique identification to your computer and may be used for security purposes, to facilitate transactions, to personalize the website, or to gather information about the visit.

###  Disclosure of your nonpublic personal information

Commongood Careers does not disclose personal information to any third parties, except as disclosed in this Policy. Specifically, we may share the personal information that we collect with the following entities:

  * To the employer that is hiring for a specified position, when you apply for that position via the Job Board
  * To government agencies and law enforcement officials, when we are required to do so to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or when Commongood Careers in its sole discretion, believes it is required or appropriate in order to comply with the law
  * To strategic partners to evaluate trends in the marketplace on an aggregated basis, with the certainty that individual personal information will not be disclosed.

We also reserve the right to disclose personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Commongood Careers’ Terms and Conditions or other agreements, or as otherwise required or permitted by law. If Commongood Careers merges with another organization, your personal information will be acquired by that organization.

###  Use of nonpublic personal information within Commongood Careers

Commongood Careers uses personal information collected from Users in order to administer the Services requested by you, to make the Website more useful, to respond to your queries, and to inform you of new products and services offered on the Website. We also may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and administer the Website.

Your Internet Protocol address and information regarding the web pages on the Website that you visit, or that linked to the Website, may also be used to gather broad demographic information, interests, and behavior so that we may better understand our users. This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve the Website’s design and functionality. Commongood Careers may share aggregated demographic, product usage, or traffic pattern information for marketing purposes with other organizations, but these statistics will include no personal information. Except as noted above, your personal information will not be shared with other organizations for marketing purposes without your consent.

###  Security

Although the Website has security measures in place to protect against unauthorized access to and the loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control, we cannot guarantee that such security measures will be sufficient, will not be breached, and that your personal information or other information may not be disclosed or otherwise accessed in an unauthorized manner. Certain information, including personal information, may be transmitted by you and to you by unsecured electronic mail. Although it may be illegal to intercept or disclose these messages, these transmissions are not secured.  
How to update your information

You may update your information and contact preferences by sending an e-mail to [help@commongoodcareers.org](mailto:help@commongoodcareers.org) with changes to your information and contact preferences. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making changes to your information or preferences.

###  Opt-out policy

You may at any time request not to be contacted by Commongood Careers. “Opt out” requests should be sent to the address indicated on the materials sent by Commongood Careers or by replying to the email in which such material was sent.  
Linked Internet websites

The Website provides hypertext links to and framed content from other websites that may be governed by privacy policies that are different from those provided herein. If you leave the Website, or if you are presented with a framed web page that is branded with the marks of a third party, this Policy will not apply. You should read the privacy policies of websites reached through the use of links or reached through the interactions with framed content on the Website. Commongood Careers is not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through those websites, and Commongood Careers expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

###  Changes to this Policy

Changes to this Policy may be made from time to time. If a change is made, the updated policy will be posted on the Website. We encourage you to review this Policy periodically. Questions and comments about this policy may be submitted via email to [help@commongoodcareers.org](mailto:help@commongoodcareers.org).

###  Equal Opportunity Employment

We also request (but do not require) that you disclose to us your gender, race and whether or not you are a veteran or are disabled, for the sole purpose of assisting us to satisfy certain government reporting requirements. We keep this information strictly confidential, do not use it in any of our decision-making processes, and do not share it with anyone (including employers with whom we work) except in connection with these reporting requirements.

###  Conditions of Use

By using the Website, you agree to the terms and conditions contained in this Policy and/or any other agreement that we might have with you. If you do not agree to any of these terms and conditions, you should not use the Website or any of our services. You agree that any dispute over privacy or the terms contained in this Policy, or any other agreement we have with you, will be governed by the laws of the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, and you agree that any such dispute will be adjudicated by the courts in the Commonwealth of Massachusetts, and you agree to abide by any limitation on damages contained in any agreement we may have with you.

This Policy was last updated in May 2015.
